<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Clarity Docs on Compose Docs</title><link>https://example.com/docs/clarity/</link><description>Recent content in Clarity Docs on Compose Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://example.com/docs/clarity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting started</title><link>https://example.com/docs/clarity/getting-started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/docs/clarity/getting-started/</guid><description>Prerequisites Firstly, ensure you have installed the extended version of Hugo. See installation steps from Hugo's official docs.
Getting up and running Read the prerequisites above and verify you're using the extended version of Hugo. There are at least two ways of quickly getting started with Hugo and the VMware Clarity theme:
Option 1 (recommended) Generate a new Hugo site and add this theme as a Git submodule inside your themes folder:</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://example.com/docs/clarity/features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/docs/clarity/features/</guid><description>Blog with tagging and category options
Deeplinks
Native Image Lazy Loading
Customizable (see config)
Dark Mode (with UI controls for user preference setting)
Toggleable table of contents
Flexible image configuration
Logo alignment
Mobile support with configurable menu alignment
Syntax Highlighting
Rich code block functions including:
Copy to clipboard Toggle line wrap (dynamic) Toggle line numbers Language label Toggle block expansion/contraction (dynamic) To put it all in context, here is a preview showing all functionality.</description></item><item><title>Customization</title><link>https://example.com/docs/clarity/customize/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/docs/clarity/customize/</guid><description>Configuration If set, jump over to the config.toml file and start configuring your site.
This section will mainly cover settings that are unique to this theme. If something is not covered here (or elsewhere in this file), there's a good chance it is covered in this Hugo docs page.
Global Parameters These options set global values that some pages or all pages in the site use by default.
Parameter Value Type Overidable on Page author string no twitter string no largeTwitterCard boolean no ga_analytics string no description string yes introDescription string no numberOfTagsShown integer no fallBackOgImage file path (string) no codeMaxLines integer yes codeLineNumbers boolean yes mainSections array/string no centerLogo boolean no logo file path (string) no mobileNavigation string no figurePositionShow boolean yes figurePositionLabel string no customCSS array of file path (string) no customJS array of file path (string) no enforceLightMode boolean N/A enforceDarkMode boolean N/A titleSeparator string no comment boolean no Page Parameters These options can be set from a page frontmatter or via archetypes.</description></item><item><title>Manipulating Images</title><link>https://example.com/docs/clarity/images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/docs/clarity/images/</guid><description>Images Image figure captions You have the option of adding captions to images in blog posts and automatically prepending a desired string such as &amp;quot;Figure N&amp;quot; to the alt text. This is controlled via two global settings.
figurePositionLabel is a string which will be prepended to any alt text of an article image. By default, this is set to &amp;quot;Figure.&amp;quot; And figurePositionShow controls, globally, whether to show this label. It does not affect whether to show the image alt text, only the prefix figure caption.</description></item><item><title>Blogging</title><link>https://example.com/docs/clarity/blogging/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/docs/clarity/blogging/</guid><description>Blog directory Edit the config.toml file and change the mainSections key. Values will be directories where the blogs reside.
1 2 3 4 [params]...mainSections = [&amp;#34;posts&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;docs&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;blogs&amp;#34;]... For more info, see the Hugo docs.
Mobile menu positioning The navigation menu when mobile browsing can be configured in config.toml to open right or left depending on preference. The &amp;quot;hamburger&amp;quot; menu icon will always display in the upper right hand corner regardless.</description></item><item><title>Syntax Highlighting</title><link>https://example.com/docs/clarity/syntax-highlighting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/docs/clarity/syntax-highlighting/</guid><description>Code Display line numbers Choose whether to display line numbers within a code block globally with the parameter codeLineNumbers setting to true or false.
1 2 3 4 [params]...codeLineNumbers = true# Shows line numbers for all code blocks globally.... Limit code block height You can globally control the number of lines which are displayed by default for your code blocks. Code which has the number of lines exceed this value will dynamically cause two code block expansion buttons to appear, allowing the user to expand to full length and contract.</description></item><item><title>Theme Overrides</title><link>https://example.com/docs/clarity/theme-overrides/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/docs/clarity/theme-overrides/</guid><description>Custom CSS and JS To minimize HTTP requests per page, we would recommend loading CSS styles and JavaScript helpers in single bundles. That is to say, one CSS file and one JavaScript file. Using Hugo minify functions, these files will be minified to optimize the size.
Going by the above 👆🏻 reason, we recommend adding custom CSS and JS via this custom SASS file and custom JavaScript file.
However, sometimes you may need to load additional style or script files.</description></item></channel></rss>